Guide to the Robert College records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series II: Heritage Room/Rare Books (Istanbul & R.C./N.Y. Offices)
  - History – Marcia Stevens (Box 85)
  - Hisar Foundation (Box 85)
  - Kemer School--Hisar Foundation (Box 85)
  - 1973 Agreement Between Trustees of RC and Hisar Vakfi (Box 85)
  - Land Transferred to RC/Vakif (Box 85)
  - Land, "Triangle" Land, Huntington Estate (Box 85)
  - Turkish Law #625 (1984) (Box 85)
  - Community School (Box 85)
  - Correspondence re: Termination of IIS Membership (Box 85)
  - Page, Childs, Warner: Second Follow-Up Memo to "Report on Archive Files Remaining on RC Campus" (Box 85)
  - Old Photographs: (Box 86)
    - Identified Photos (Box 86)
    - RC/ACG Theater/Music (Box 86)
    - RC Students Extracurricular/Sports (Box 86)
    - RC Students, Informal (Box 86)
    - RC Administrators, Faculty (Box 86)
    - RC Students at Work (Box 86)
    - ACG Faculty/Administrators (Box 86)
    - ACG Students, Informal (Alumnae) (Box 86)
    - ACG Negatives - Students at Work (Box 86)
    - ACG Extracurricular/Sports (Box 86)
    - RC/ACG Negatives – Trustees (1960s) (Box 86)
    - RC/ACG Trustees (Box 86)
    - RC/ACG Negatives – Language Lab (Box 86)
    - Computer Center (Box 86)
    - Robert College Post-1971 (Box 86)
    - ACG - Campus (Box 86)
    - RC – Campus (Box 86)
    - RC – Post-1971 Campus, includes Gould Hall (color negatives) (Box 86)
    - Robert College Post-1971 Campus & Students (Box 86)
  - Old Photographs: (Box 87)
    - Trustees, Alumni/Friends – Adana, May 1985 – Izmir, 1985 (Box 87)
    - Trustees, 1980s – Istanbul – General (Box 87)
    - Early Years – negs w/out originals (general) (Box 87)
    - Scutari Negative, 8x10 – made from print borrowed from Bettman Archives (Box 87)
    - Negatives without originals (made for December 1985 exhibit) (Box 87)
    - Negatives made from slides – The Irade, Halide Edip reading father’s palm (Box 87)
    - Bebek and Early Years – Negatives from documents in the archives (Box 87)
    - RC Campus – Negatives made for December 1985 exhibit (Box 87)
    - ACG – Gould Hall – Negatives made for December 1985 exhibit (Box 87)
    - Xeroxes & photos from Bettman Archive made for December Exhibit (Box 87)
    - Negatives of photos taken by Grady Hobson (Box 87)
    - Negatives & photos, sent from Turkey by May Fincanci (December 1985) (Box 87)
  - Photographs: (Box 88)
    - School and Negatives (Box 88)
    - Campus and Calendar (1945) (Box 88)
    - Campus (incl. Bebek) and Negatives (Box 88)
    - Student Life/Activities (Box 88)
    - City/Campus/Aerial Views (1878 1905 1926) (Box 88)
    - Group/Individual Portraits (Box 88)
    - Graduation Portraits (1937 1949 1963) (Box 88)
    - Turkey (1985) (Box 88)
    - Dams and Waterworks (October 1967) (Box 88)
    - Hamlin Portrait (April 1993) (Box 88)
    - London Reception (January 1995) (Box 88)
    - Washington Reception (January 1995) (Box 88)
    - Colony Club, NYC (Trustee/Alumni Reception) (Nov 30, 1994) (Box 88)
    - Borden Furniture (Box 88)
    - Misc.-Artifacts, Exchange Students, Trees (Box 88)
    - Covers and stamps (Box 88)
    - Photos of Cistern (Nov 5, 1992) (Box 88)
    - Dining Pavileai-Mark and Nedret Butler Mimarlav (Box 88)
    - Hand-drawn plans (Box 88)
    - Alterations to Arnavutkoy Campus/1971 Report (1971) (Box 88)
    - Report with Special Reference to School of Business and Economics (Sept 20, 1967) (Box 88)
    - Proportioned Spatial Relationship Diagram (Library/Gould Hall) (1991) (Box 88)
    - Gould Bridge (Plans) (18 June, 1992) (Box 88)
    - Auditorium Plans and Sound System Specifications (1988) (Box 88)
  - New Auditorium-Gymnasium-Science Building (April 20, 1988) (2 Folders) (Box 89)
  - Science and Engineering Building-Scale Drawings and Specifications (Nov 20, 1958) (Box 89)
  - Science and Engineering Building-Preliminary Drawings (1958) (Box 89)
  - Preliminary Master Plan (Dec 20 1955) (Box 90)
  - Plans of School Buildings (Compiled 1990) (Box 90)
  - Master Plan for Buildings and Grounds (Oct 1992) (Box 90)
  - More Plans (August 1992) (Box 90)
  - Plans of School Buildings (Box 90)
  - Central Heating System of American Robert Lyce (Box 90)
  - Headmaster's Report-Benjamin D. Williams III (Jan/Feb 1993) (Box 90)
  - Headmaster's Report (Jan 1992 Jan 1995 May 1995) (Box 90)
  - Publications & Magazines, Misc. (Box 90)
  - Trustee's Report from Jim Maggart (1978-1979) (Box 90)
  - Correspondence (ca. 1960) (2 Folders) (Box 91)
  - Chronology/Historical Facts for Alumni (Box 91)
  - American College for Girls, History and Speeches/Secretary's Report, Nov 15, 1927 (Box 91)
  - Hand-Made Publications (Box 91)
  - Publicity/News Articles (incl. Tansu Ciller) (Box 91)
  - List of articles re: Turkey's critics (Box 91)
  - Material taken from book of Gates Family Letters and Diaries (Box 91)
  - The World of Robert College (VHS-written and narrated by Talat S. Halman) (1986) (Box 91)
- Series III: Board of Trustees and Specific Committees
  - Investment Committee (1971-1972) (Box 5)
  - Executive Council of the Trustees: Meetings/Reports (1973) (Box 5)
  - Memoranda from Jane Page/Catherine Rose to Board Members (1973) (Box 5)
  - "Situation Reports" to the Board of Trustees from Catherine Rose and Jane Page (1973) (Box 5)
  - Board of Trustees-Minutes, Memoranda (1973) (Box 5)
  - Executive Committee, Ogden Minute (1973) (Box 5)
  - Minutes/Situation Reports (1972) (Box 5)
  - Minutes from Executive Committee; Investment Committee; A.I.D. (Box 5)
  - Report (1972) (Box 5)
  - Executive Committee/Board Minutes; Report of Investment Committee (1972) (Box 5)
  - Distribution of Material: Trustee's Annual Reports (1971) (Box 5)
  - Distribution of Material: Letters/reports from N.Y. Office; Istanbul (December 1971) (Box 5)
  - Memoranda sent by Catherine Rose (1972) (Box 5)
  - End-of-year Report, Financial statement; Catherine Rose, Jane Page, Chairman (1972) (Box 5)
  - Correspondence/Reports, incl. Annual Report of Trustees, A.I.D. Report (1971) (Box 5)
  - Distribution of Material to Board: Minutes from Committee Meetings (1971) (Box 5)
  - Board of Trustees: Memoranda/Situation Reports/Minutes (1971) (Box 5)
- Series IV: Board of Trustees and Financial Documents
  - Soliciting Contributions, cover letter from James Lawrence (1971) (Box 6)
  - Minutes of Board /Executive Council/Situation Reports from Chairman (1971) (Box 6)
  - Memos/Minutes of Executive Committee, Cover letters from Rose/Lawrence (1971) (Box 6)
  - Memoranda, "Situation" Reports from Trustees (1971) (Box 6)
  - Correspondence with Thomas Pope, Controller (1971-1974) (Box 6)
  - Board of Trustees: Situation Reports, minutes, Memoranda (1970) (Box 6)
  - Memoranda to from Rose/Lawrence: Situation Reports, Financial Statements (1970) (Box 6)
  - Board of Trustees: Minutes, Reports, Memoranda, cover letters from Lawrence (1970) (Box 6)
  - Catherine Scott Rose: General Correspondence (1968-1978) (Box 6)
  - Helen White, Correspondence (1973) (2 Folders) (Box 6)
  - Correspondence to Helen White, Controller (1974) (Box 6)
  - Correspondence to Helen White, Controller (1974) (Box 6)
- Series V: Faculty Lists
  - Adamson, Dorothy (Box 10)
  - Adamson, Robert (Box 10)
  - Ainsworth,, Laurence P. (RCCS) (Box 10)
  - Akgerman, Aydin (Box 10)
  - Akgor, Rhoda (Box 10)
  - Akyurek, Susan (Box 10)
  - Alemdar, Nigar (Box 10)
  - Altug, Erol (Box 10)
  - Altunbas, Joan (Box 10)
  - Anderson, Paul (Box 10)
  - Anthony, James W. (Box 10)
  - Arndt, Alice (Box 10)
  - Arndt, Robert (Box 10)
  - Arnold, Dennis (Box 10)
  - Artun, Cigdem (Box 10)
  - Ashover, Dorothy (Box 10)
  - Asner, Bernard (Box 10)
  - Asner, Luise K. (RCCS) (Box 10)
  - Atakan, Nancy (Box 10)
  - Atalya, Nuket E. (Box 10)
  - Atay, Belinda (Box 10)
  - Atkinson, Polly P. (RCCS) (Box 10)
  - Atkinson, Thomas H. (Box 10)
  - Austin, Susan (Box 10)
  - Backer, Jane E. (RCCS) (Box 10)
  - Bailey, James M., Jr. (Box 10)
  - Baker, Barbara L. (Box 10)
  - Bakkalcioglu, Chantal (RCCS) (Box 10)
  - Banck, Robert P. (Box 10)
  - Banister, Cheryl (RCCS) (Box 10)
  - Banister, Michael E. (Box 10)
  - Barkanic, Stephen (RCCS) (Box 10)
  - Barnes, Nelson R. (Box 10)
  - Barrett, Peter (Box 10)
  - Barry, Donald (Box 10)
  - Barry, Roxanne (Box 10)
  - Barry, William D. (Box 10)
  - Barstow, Leon E. (Box 10)
  - Basaran, Sumru (Box 10)
  - Beaudin, Suzanne F. (Box 10)
  - Beck, Anne T. (Box 10)
  - Beeley, Mary (Box 10)
  - Beets, Cornelis (Box 10)
  - Belknap, Bruce J. (Box 10)
  - Bell, Dixie L. (Box 10)
  - Bell, Donald A. (Box 10)
  - Bell, Graydon D. (Box 10)
  - Ben, Necla (Box 10)
  - Berkman, Mary (Box 10)
  - Berner, Robert F. (Box 10)
  - Bernhardt, David (Box 10)
  - Bernier, Henri (Box 10)
  - Berry Kenneth (Box 10)
  - Biersteker, Joseph J. (Box 10)
  - Biggers, Ursula (Box 10)
  - Blake, Ann B. (Box 10)
  - Blake, Wilson K. (Box 10)
  - Bleyler, Susan S. (Box 10)
  - Block, James (Box 10)
  - Bloor, Gillian (Box 10)
  - Boling, Glenn (Box 10)
  - Bond, Susan M. (London) (Box 10)
  - Boyce, Mattie (Box 10)
  - Bozhuyuk, Mehmet Emin (Box 10)
  - Bradley, Ruth (Box 10)
  - Brainerd, James (Box 10)
  - Bray, Douglas (RCCS) (Box 10)
  - Bray, Susan (RCCS) (Box 10)
  - Breen, Martin C. (Box 10)
  - Brzozowski, Witold (Box 10)
  - Buchanan, Olive (Box 10)
  - Burrows, Edward L. (Box 10)
  - Burton, Belinda (Box 10)
  - Buskey, Frederick (Box 10)
  - Buskey, Pamela (Box 10)
  - Calkins, Costantia H. (Box 11)
  - Cameron, Robert (RCCS) (Box 11)
  - Canli, Linda L. (Box 11)
  - Cano, Janet M. (Box 11)
  - Capre, Raymond (Box 11)
  - Capre, Sabine (RCCS) (Box 11)
  - Carey, Anthony (Box 11)
  - Carlson, Robert S. (Box 11)
  - Carrell, Donna (Box 11)
  - Carrell, Lloyd (Box 11)
  - Carson, Michael J. (Box 11)
  - Casker, David E. (Box 11)
  - Chapman, John K. (Box 11)
  - Christensen, Robert (Box 11)
  - Christoe, Charles (Box 11)
  - Clark, Ronald (Box 11)
  - Chrysoyelos, Aglaia (Box 11)
  - Clarke, Rosamund (Box 11)
  - Clarke, Valerie J. (RCCS) (Box 11)
  - Clarkson, John E. (Box 11)
  - Clement, Meredith O. (Box 11)
  - Coffey, Margaret (Box 11)
  - Collins, Barbara (RCCS) (Box 11)
  - Collins, Douglas L. (Box 11)
  - Collins, Thomas J. (Box 11)
  - Coronis, Julia (Julie) (Box 11)
  - Corrie, Bruce (Box 11)
  - Cosma, Barbara J. (Box 11)
  - Crocker, Edwin L. (Box 11)
  - Crockett, Dr. George (Box 11)
  - Crowe, Nigel P. (Box 11)
  - Crowell, Julian (Box 11)
  - Crowell, Roberta (RCCS) (Box 11)
  - Culp, Phyllis (Box 11)
  - Curcuru, Gerald (Box 11)
  - Dabanovich, Elizabeth (Box 11)
  - Damon, George (Box 11)
  - Davies, Peter (Box 11)
  - Davis, Brian E. (Box 11)
  - Davis, Thomas (Box 11)
  - Davis, Trudy (Box 11)
  - Dawe, Virginia P. (Box 11)
  - Day, Melvin H. (Box 11)
  - Demci, Jermen (Box 11)
  - Denicola, John (Box 11)
  - Derba, Victor (Box 11)
  - Dewey, Helen (Box 11)
  - Dewey, Richard H. (Box 11)
  - Diehl, Jocelyn (Box 11)
  - Donnelly, Margaret (Box 11)
  - Donahue, Patrick A. (Box 11)
  - Donohue, Mimi (Box 11)
  - Donohue, Robert J. (Box 11)
  - Donougher, Yvonne (RCCS) (Box 11)
  - Downes, Donald C. (Box 11)
  - Downie, Norville M. (Box 11)
  - Downing, Bruce T. (Box 11)
  - Dunbar, Eileen (Box 11)
  - Dunbar, Terry F. (Box 11)
  - Dunlap, Richard M. (Box 11)
  - Dunn, Irving J. (Box 11)
  - Duren, Ann Scott (Box 11)
  - Durfee, William H. (Box 11)
  - Durst, Leon H. (Box 11)
  - Eames, William A. (Box 11)
  - Eastwood, Robert P. (Box 11)
  - Ebaugh, William C. (Box 11)
  - Eberly, Donald J. (Box 11)
  - Edmonds, Anna (RCCS) (Box 11)
  - Eells, James (Box 11)
  - Eisner, Bette (Box 11)
  - Elbow,, Matthew H. (Box 11)
  - Eldridge, Rodney W. (Box 11)
  - Elliott, Margaret J. (Box 11)
  - Ellis, Ellen D. (Box 11)
  - Ellison, Clifford (Box 11)
  - Emerson, Howard (Box 11)
  - Emerson, Mark F. (Box 11)
  - Emery, Ronald (Box 11)
  - Enders, Abbie G. (Box 11)
  - English, John M. (Box 11)
  - English, Betty R. (Box 11)
  - Epting, Richard S. (Box 11)
  - Erben, M. Talat (Box 11)
  - Erdman, Frederick S. (Box 11)
  - Erdogan, Tamay (Box 11)
  - Erkel, Oya (Box 11)
  - Erma, Victor A. (Box 11)
  - Ertuna, Ibrahim O. (Box 11)
  - Erul, Zeynep (Box 11)
  - Ervin, Sue (Box 11)
  - Espy, John (Box 11)
  - Essenberg, Christine (Box 11)
  - Estes, Charles (Box 11)
  - Etcheson, Warren (Box 11)
  - Etz, Katherine (Box 11)
  - Evans, Curtis G. (Box 11)
  - Evans, Llewellyn T. (Box 11)
  - Ewing, Doris I. (Box 11)
  - Farber, Dennis (Box 12)
  - Farrior, Bonnie Lee (Box 12)
  - Faussett, Janice A. (Box 12)
  - Faust, John D. (Box 12)
  - Faust, Richard L. (Box 12)
  - Fenske, Robert M. (Box 12)
  - Ferrell, Georgia D. (Box 12)
  - Ferry, John A. (Box 12)
  - Fertig, Earl A. (Box 12)
  - Fessler, Robert (RCCS) (Box 12)
  - Field, Edmund (Box 12)
  - Firstenberger, Betty Lou (Box 12)
  - Fischer, Barbara (Box 12)
  - Fischer, Jeffrey (Box 12)
  - Fisher, Edgar J. (Box 12)
  - Fisher, J. Elliott (Box 12)
  - Fisher, Larry R. (Box 12)
  - Fisher, Maija (Box 12)
  - Fisher, Sydney N. (Box 12)
  - Fiske, John C. (Box 12)
  - Flach, Garold J. (Box 12)
  - Flanagan, Kevin (Box 12)
  - Fleming, Gordon H. (Box 12)
  - Flint, Calvin C. (Box 12)
  - Flodin, Ivan A. (Box 12)
  - Flory, Paul M. (Box 12)
  - Flonger, Lee A. (Box 12)
  - Foreman, Alastair (Box 12)
  - Forsgren, Eva (Box 12)
  - Forsgren, Robert (Box 12)
  - Fosdicck, Edith W. (Box 12)
  - Foster, Frances A. (Box 12)
  - Fotos, Evan (Box 12)
  - Fox, Robert L. (Box 12)
  - Franck, Peter (Box 12)
  - Frank, Carol (Box 12)
  - Franks, Elizabeth (Box 12)
  - Freeburg, Dorothy Dumble (Box 12)
  - Freely, Dolores (Box 12)
  - Freely, John B. (Box 12)
  - Frewen, Ione (Box 12)
  - Frewen, Katherine (Box 12)
  - Frey, Donald A. (Box 12)
  - Frisinger, Ann Louise (Box 12)
  - Frost, Elisabeth S. (Box 12)
  - Frouxides, Sypros (Box 12)
  - Fuchs, Traugott (Box 12)
  - Fuller, David R. (Box 12)
  - Fulmer, Jervis M. (Box 12)
  - Funk, G. Ann (Box 12)
  - Gale, Charles (Box 12)
  - Galloway, Ian R. (Box 12)
  - Cambell, Janet C. (Box 12)
  - Ganley, Harry P. (Box 12)
  - Gann, Charles (Box 12)
  - Gardiner, Lee O. (Box 12)
  - Gareis, Fritzie E. (Box 12)
  - Garner, Glen (Box 12)
  - Garwood, David A. (Box 12)
  - Garwood, Arminet (RCCS) (Box 12)
  - Gates, Caleb F., Jr. (Box 12)
  - Gehlhar, Norman (Mrs.) (Box 12)
  - George, Dorthea (Box 12)
  - Gersten, Leon (Box 12)
  - Gesler, Wilbert M. (Box 12)
  - Getman, Susan (Box 12)
  - Ghiradelli, Robert G. (Box 12)
  - Gibb, Edward (Box 12)
  - Gibson, Margaret J. (Box 12)
  - Gilchrist, Charles W. (Box 12)
  - Gilchrist, Frances G. (Box 12)
  - Gillard, David H. (Box 12)
  - Gillis, William E., Jr. (Box 12)
  - Gilman, Irene P. (Box 12)
  - Gilman, William H. (Box 12)
  - Glashow, Harvey A. (Box 12)
  - Glidewell, Dora J. (Box 12)
  - Gnade, Richard E. (Box 12)
  - Gobby, Margaret A. (Box 13)
  - Goksel, Elizabeth B. (Box 13)
  - Goldberg, Jack L. (Box 13)
  - Golden, Daniel P. (Box 13)
  - Goldman, Haskell E. (Box 13)
  - Gonul, Betty N. (Box 13)
  - Goodwin, Francis G. (Box 13)
  - Gozubuyuk, Shafiga D. (Box 13)
  - Grady, Dennis (RCCS) (Box 13)
  - Grant, Samuel B., Jr. (Box 13)
  - Graves, Ellen T. (Box 13)
  - Green, Barbara (Box 13)
  - Green, Michael D. (Box 13)
  - Greenwood, Keith M. (Box 13)
  - Greer, Sharron (Box 13)
  - Griffin, Genevieve R. (Box 13)
  - Griswold, Paul H. (Box 13)
  - Gronewald, Benjamin F. (Box 13)
  - Groteluschen, Jon K. (Box 13)
  - Grover, Kathryn W. (Box 13)
  - Grunder, Ann E. (Box 13)
  - Gulcur, Fazil (Box 13)
  - Guleryuz, Carol (Box 13)
  - Gunay, Guniz (Box 13)
  - Gurmen, Marjorie (Box 13)
  - Gurney, Caroline L. (Box 13)
  - Gustafson, Peter B. (Box 13)
  - Gustafson, Sandra M. (Box 13)
  - Gustavson, Eric D. (Box 13)
  - Hackett, Susan (RCCS) (Box 13)
  - Haines, Donald B. (Box 13)
  - Hall, Howard P. (Box 13)
  - Hall, Mrs. Jack (RCCS) (Box 13)
  - Hall, Julia B. (Box 13)
  - Hall, Rachel (RCCS) (Box 13)
  - Hamel, Paul E. (Box 13)
  - Hamilton, Michael (Box 13)
  - Hamilton, Suzanne (Box 13)
  - Hammond, Thom (Box 13)
  - Hanna, Clyde James (Box 13)
  - Hanopulos, Waltraud (Box 13)
  - Hanrahan, Thomas D. (Box 13)
  - Hansen, Claude G., Jr. (Box 13)
  - Hansen, Diana W. (Box 13)
  - Hanson, David O. (Box 13)
  - Hanson, Eva G. (Box 13)
  - Hanson, Frederick W. (Box 13)
  - Hard, Roberta-Marie (Box 13)
  - Harder, Shepard (Box 13)
  - Hardin, Martin D., Jr. (Box 13)
  - Hardy, Judith (Box 13)
  - Hare, Raymond A. (Box 13)
  - Hargreaves, Minette (Box 13)
  - Harrell, Bryant E., Jr. (Box 13)
  - Harrell, Elizabeth (RCCS) (Box 13)
  - Harris, William W., II (Box 13)
  - Harrison, Martha D. (Box 13)
  - Harshbarger, Frances (Box 13)
  - Hart, Charles (Box 13)
  - Hart, Helen (Box 13)
  - Harter, Ann F. (Box 13)
  - Harter, Faith C. (Box 13)
  - Harter, Stephen P. (Box 13)
  - Harvey, Ada M. (Box 13)
  - Harvey, Julia (Box 13)
  - Hasbrouck, David L. (Box 13)
  - Haskin, Aurolee (Box 13)
  - Hathaway, Ralph R. (Box 13)
  - Hatherly, Keith H. (Box 13)
  - Hatherly, Patricia A. (Box 13)
  - Hawkins, Ruth (Box 13)
  - Hayes, George P. (Box 13)
  - Hazeltine, Burt A. (Box 13)
  - Hazleton, Willis B. (Box 13)
  - Heaney, John (Box 13)
  - Hellbronn, Denise (Box 13)
  - Heinrich, Ronald G. (Box 13)
  - Heizer, Pauline (Box 13)
  - Helms, Carl H. (Box 13)
  - Helms, Susan C. (Box 13)
  - Henderson, Ralph S. (Box 13)
  - Henderson, Sally A. (Box 13)
  - Henricks, Vera M. (Box 13)
  - Henrikson, RIchard D. (Box 13)
  - Hepler, Jane (Box 13)
  - Hepworth, Brian E. (Box 13)
  - Hepworth, Paul (Box 13)
  - Herrick, Kathryn (Box 13)
  - Hewitt, Frank L. (Box 13)
  - Heym, Richard H. (Box 14)
  - Hickman, William C. (Box 14)
  - Higgins, Eugene (Box 14)
  - Hill, Elizabeth (Box 14)
  - Hill, Walter A.L. (Box 14)
  - Hiltner, John, Jr. (Box 14)
  - HInkel, Erna E. (Box 14)
  - Hirsch, Abraham (Box 14)
  - Hitchcock, Kim (Box 14)
  - Hobson, J. Grady (Box 14)
  - Hoffman, Donald S., Jr. (Box 14)
  - Hoffman, Jane U. (Box 14)
  - Hofland, John A. (Box 14)
  - Hogendorn, Jan S. (Box 14)
  - Hollon, Donna (Box 14)
  - Holmstrom, Engin I. (Box 14)
  - Holmstrom, Robert W., Jr. (Box 14)
  - Hopkinson, Peter (RCCS) (Box 14)
  - Horn, Robert F. (Box 14)
  - Horner, Charlene (Box 14)
  - Horuluoglu, Isabel (Box 14)
  - Hotchkiss, Arland T. (Box 14)
  - Houloussi, Hussein (Box 14)
  - Houwink, Willem (Box 14)
  - Hughes, Miriam M. (Box 14)
  - Hull, Gordon F., III (Box 14)
  - Hummel, Roland L. (Box 14)
  - Humphreys, Agnes R. (Box 14)
  - Hunt, Susan C. (Box 14)
  - Hunter, Robert G. (Box 14)
  - Hunter, Susan (RCCS) (Box 14)
  - Hurley, Kent C. (Box 14)
  - Huske, Marion K. (Box 14)
  - Ilgaz, Ayse (Box 14)
  - Incealemdaroglu, Halil (Box 14)
  - Inel, Yuksel (Box 14)
  - Inscoe, Joseph K. (Box 14)
  - Isikill, Maria (Box 14)
  - Isil, Brigitte (Box 14)
  - Iz, Dorothy (Box 14)
  - Jackson, John W. (Box 14)
  - Jacobsen, Edward C. (Box 14)
  - Jacobsen, Mary L. (Box 14)
  - Jaeckel, Ralph (Box 14)
  - Jansen, Hans G. (Box 14)
  - Jaquinet, Eleanor (RCCS) (Box 14)
  - Jaquinet, Ina T. (Box 14)
  - Jaquinet, Louis (Box 14)
  - Jarrell, Peggy (Box 14)
  - Jefferry, Henrietta (Box 14)
  - Jenison, Elsie S. (Box 14)
  - John, Lenore S. (Box 14)
  - Johnson, Ada F. (Box 14)
  - Johnson, Augustus C., Jr. (Box 14)
  - Johnson, Barbara K. (Box 14)
  - Johnson, Beatrice H. (Box 14)
  - Johnson, David R. (Box 14)
  - Johnson, James A. (Box 14)
  - Johnson, Margery (Box 14)
  - Johnson, Mary L. (Box 14)
  - Johnson, Richard A. (Box 14)
  - Johnson, Robert (Box 14)
  - Johnson, Stella (RCCS) (Box 14)
  - Johnson, Stephen (Box 14)
  - Johnson, Stephen L. (Box 14)
  - Jolly, Robert P. (Box 14)
  - Jones, Alveta S. (RCCS) (Box 14)
  - Jones, Anne F. (Box 14)
  - Jones, Harley G. (Box 14)
  - Jones, Margaret H. (Box 14)
  - Jones, Robert W. (Box 14)
  - Jordan, Louis H. (Box 14)
  - Jordan, Louise (Box 14)
  - Julier, Ann L. (Box 14)
  - Kabas, Ozer (Box 15)
  - Kale, Edward W. (Box 15)
  - Kamozut, Guzey (Box 15)
  - Kanter, Leona (RCCS) (Box 15)
  - Karamessinis, Nicholas G. (Box 15)
  - Karapat, Kemal (Box 15)
  - Kaynar, Oya (Box 15)
  - Keeler, Ktephen E., Jr. (Box 15)
  - Keen, Maria E. (Box 15)
  - Keller, Erna B. (Box 15)
  - Kendall, Thomas H. (Box 15)
  - Kennard, Ralph B. (Box 15)
  - Kennedy, Anne (Box 15)
  - Kennedy, Dorothy (Box 15)
  - Kennedy, Joan E. (Box 15)
  - Kennedy, John Gerard (Box 15)
  - Kennedy, Margaret (Box 15)
  - Kent, Jeremy (Box 15)
  - Kent, Millicent F. (Box 15)
  - Kerestecioglu, Elizabeth (Box 15)
  - Kerman, Hediye F. (Box 15)
  - Kerner, Joseph R., Jr. (Box 15)
  - Kerr, E. S. Wells (Box 15)
  - Key, Mary E. (Box 15)
  - Keyes, Mary S. (Box 15)
  - Kiel, Jerry A. (Box 15)
  - Kili, Suna (Box 15)
  - Kilic, Eva (Box 15)
  - Kimball, Elsa P. (Box 15)
  - Kimball, Thomas M. (Box 15)
  - Kimball, William S. (Box 15)
  - Kimmons, John E. (Box 15)
  - Kinaci, Dorothy G. (RCCS) (Box 15)
  - King, Anna M. (Box 15)
  - King, Barbara (Box 15)
  - King, Jane M. (Box 15)
  - King, John C., Jr. (Box 15)
  - Kinkaid, Dorothy (Box 15)
  - Kirby, Fay (Box 15)
  - Kisselbach, Vincent (Box 15)
  - Klein, Jerzy (Box 15)
  - Kligman, Judith N. (RCCS) (Box 15)
  - Kligman, Ronald L. (Box 15)
  - Klopp, Charles D. (Box 15)
  - Klopp, Susan S. (Box 15)
  - Klotz, Edith L. (Box 15)
  - Knabenshue, Paul D. (Box 15)
  - Knudson, Judith L. (Box 15)
  - Koertge, Noretta (Box 15)
  - Koeth, Antonia (Box 15)
  - Kohn, Preston (Box 15)
  - Kortepeter, Carl M. (Box 15)
  - Koth, David B. (Box 15)
  - Kreider, Ethel (Box 15)
  - Ksido, Sophia (Box 15)
  - Kubilay, Hayat (Box 15)
  - Kucukcalkaz, Emily J. (Box 15)
  - Kugelman, Miriam (Box 15)
  - Kunick, Vera (Box 15)
  - Kuniholm, Peter I. (Box 15)
  - Kunkle, Ethel W. (Box 15)
  - Kunt-Beets, Ineke (RCCS) (Box 15)
  - Kunt, Metin I. (Box 15)
  - Kuntay, Esin (Box 15)
  - Kuran, Sylvia S. (Box 15)
  - Lachance, Benoit (Ben) (Box 15)
  - Lackner, Lois M. (Box 15)
  - Laguros, Joakim (Box 15)
  - Lajoie, Kenneth T. (Box 15)
  - Lair, Clinton N. (Box 15)
  - Lamb, Agnes (Box 15)
  - Lambert, Lorene (Box 15)
  - Lamotte, Carol (Box 15)
  - Lancaster, Susan (Box 15)
  - Lanckton, Arthur L. (Box 15)
  - Landes, Margaret W. (Box 15)
  - Lane, Herbert H. (Box 15)
  - Lauman, William M. (Box 15)
  - Lawrence, Margaret R. (RCCS) (Box 15)
  - Mendenhall, Leone R. (Box 16)
  - Menzel, Southard (Box 16)
  - Mergy, Pamela (Box 16)
  - Merrick, William M. (Box 16)
  - Merriell, David M. (Box 16)
  - Merriell, Grant W. (Box 16)
  - Meservey, Edward B. (Box 16)
  - Meyer, Ralph (RCCS) (Box 16)
  - Mikases, Irving F. (Box 16)
  - Miles, George C. (Box 16)
  - Miles, Helen (Box 16)
  - Miller, Bernetta A. (Box 16)
  - Miller, George A. (Box 16)
  - Miller, Harold J. (Box 16)
  - Miller, Sara S. (Box 16)
  - Miller, Walter M. (Box 16)
  - Miller, William S., Jr. (Box 16)
  - Milnor, Joseph K., Jr. (Box 16)
  - Minarovich, Betty M. (Box 16)
  - Miner, Robert G., Jr. (Box 16)
  - Minifie, Jonathan (Box 16)
  - Mitchell, Alan R. (Box 16)
  - Mitchell, Linda L. (Box 16)
  - Mlcoh, Carlo O. (Box 16)
  - Mlcoh, Giovanna (Box 16)
  - Mondics, Margaret (Box 16)
  - Monjikov, Mary W. (Box 16)
  - Monroe, Mildred I. (Box 16)
  - de Montoliu, Lucia (Box 16)
  - Mooney, E. Jean (Box 16)
  - Moore, Alice (RCCS) (Box 16)
  - Moor, Karen (Box 16)
  - Moore, Laurence (Box 16)
  - Moore, Thomas R. (Box 16)
  - Mordan, Mary Jane (Box 16)
  - Moreau, Henri L. (Box 16)
  - Morgan, Alfred L. (Box 16)
  - Morley, Peter W. (Box 16)
  - Morrill, Martha (Box 16)
  - Morris, Deborah R. (RCCS) (Box 16)
  - Morse, Louis S., Jr. (Box 16)
  - Morse, Susan K. (Box 16)
  - Moulton, Elizabeth P. (Box 16)
  - Mudie-Yuvanidi, Helen (Box 16)
  - Muhlhausen, Edgar K. (Box 16)
  - Murphy, Carol J. (Box 16)
  - Murphy, Mitzi M. (Box 16)
  - Murphy, Richard A (Box 16)
  - Murray, Edward S. (Box 16)
  - Murray, William S. (Box 16)
  - Mussell, Alan E. (Box 16)
  - Muther, Richard (Box 16)